Revelation 12:17 the title of the
message Revelation 12:7 the Bible says
here and the
dragon was wroth with the woman and went
to make war with the remnant of her
seed which keep the Commandments of God
and have the testimony of
Jesus the Bible here describes this
scene of the Dragon who we known to be a
symbol of
Satan being angry and going after the
people of
God we know that a time is coming in
which there is going to
be serious
conflict on this
Earth in Revelation
13:3 speaking towards this same end the
Bible says and I saw one of his heads as
it were wounded to death and his deadly
wound was healed and all the world
wondered after the who the
Beast and they worshiped the dragon
which gave power unto the Beast and they
worshiped the Beast saying who is like
unto the Beast who is able to make war
with him that's the question this power
is so enormous this power is so
overwhelming the question is asked who
is able to make make war with the
Beast come back with me to the Book of
Daniel 12 because in Daniel 12 and verse
one Speaking of this same event the
Bible says in verse one and that and at
that time Michael shall stand up the
great Prince which standeth for the
children of thy people and there shall
be a time of trouble such as never was
since there was a nation even to that
same time and at that time thy people
shall be delivered
everyone that shall be found written in
the book The Bible tells us there will
be a time of trouble let me ask you a
question how many of you are preparing
for that time of
trouble how many of you understand
how important that time is how important
it is that that you and I must be ready
to face that time
and beloved I I fear you know I don't
know if you've ever heard this but have
you have you ever heard anyone say
Adventist say man I don't want to be
alive during the time of trouble you
ever heard one anyone say that I don't
want to be around during the time of
trouble because it's going to be so bad
because we're going to have to deal with
with this Beast who is like unto the
Beast who's able to make war with him
we're going to have to deal with this
Dragon we're going to have to deal with
these powers and it and it seems just so
crazy I just don't want to be around I
would
rather be in my
grave I would rather have it
easy I don't want to face these Powers I
don't want to face this time beloved I
fear that for many of us we are
approaching this from a
totally wrong
perspective come back with me to the
Book of Genesis chapter 1 our key text
for today Genesis 1 and verse
26 Genesis chapter 1 and verse
[Music]
26 the Bible says here and God
said let us make man in our
what in our image after our what
likeness and let them have dominion over
the fish of the sea and over the foul of
the air and over the cattle and over all
the Earth and over every creeping thing
that creepeth upon the Earth let us read
that
again let's read it together the Bible
says and God said let us make man in our
image and after our
likeness and let them have dominion over
the fish of the sea and over
the and over the and Over All all the
Earth and over every creeping thing that
creepeth upon the
earth when God made
man he made him in his
image I want you to notice something
here because the text here describes two
kingdoms how many kingdoms everyone two
first of all God said let us
make man there is a kingdom of man
what is the other Kingdom in this
text come on it's right there not only
did God create man but he also created
an so we have the Animal Kingdom in this
text is that correct so God created man
the kingdom of man and then God created
the animal
kingdom and when God created Man In His
Image God gave man the
dominion over the
animals come come with me notice with me
the Bible says let us make man in our
image and after our likeness what does
it mean when God said let us make man in
our image and after our
likeness rephrase that for me God said
let us make man in our image and in our
likeness what does that mean
what was he saying let us make
man let us make man like
us let us make man like
us so so so in the likeness of God means
that God made man
Godlike is that
right okay some of you look a little
nervous like
Godlike beloved Godlike is not
God are you with me so so so God made
man Godlike or like God but man was not
God let us make man in our likeness let
us make man to resemble us let us make
man like us so so man was was was made
like God but was not
God man was made in Perfection man was
made in Holiness so man was like God and
that's what it means to be in his
likeness or In His
Image now notice when God was in His
image and in his likeness he had
dominion over the fish of the sea and
over the foul of the air and over the
the the the Beast of the Earth are you
with me when God made Man In His Image
when God made man under under God's rule
man was King of the earth and man ruled
over the animals man had Dominion man
had what everyone dominion over the
animals
however Satan came into the
picture you see when God created man he
gave man dominion over
everything over what everyone everything
except one
thing what did man not have dominion
over let me rephrase it who did man not
have dominion
over
God God gave man dominion over
everything hey you rule this Earth you
have dominion over the animals but you
are subject to to
me so the one thing man did not have was
dominion over God he was like God but he
was not
God come with me to Genesis CH
3:5 Genesis chapter 3 and verse 5 and
you know the story this serpent this
what everyone what is a serpent what
would you classify that
as okay just on a broad level it's an
animal it's an animal it's of the Animal
Kingdom so God used this Serpent and and
I'm sorry Satan uses Serpent and comes
to Eve and and notice with me verse five
for God does know that in the day that
you eat thereof then your eyes shall be
opened and you shall be what as Gods
knowing good and
evil now I want you to check this out
guys
because the text does not actually say
you shall be as Gods the word as isn't
in the
text what Satan was saying to Adam and
Eve is you
shall be
come God
all right guys listen
carefully when God made man he made him
to
be like God Satan says no you should
be come
God that was that's what he was offering
Adam and you
can forget about being like God
God why don't you
be come
God and when Adam and Eve fell for this
lie when they when they reached out to
not be like God but to be come
God that's When sin
entered and let me ask you something
when sin entered did man lose
Dominion okay so watch this the moment
that man reached out to grab the one
thing he did not have dominion over he
suddenly lost dominion over
everything he lost dominion over the
animal kingdom check this out come with
me to Genesis 3 and verse
22 Genesis 3:22 and I want you to notice
this because this this is quite amazing
Genesis 3: 22 the Bible says and and the
Lord God said behold the man is what is
become
as one of
us that kind of seems strange in light
of what we're talking about behold the
man is
become as one of us like one of us wait
a minute God you just told us that you
made man like one of us
are you with me there's a little
confusion here because how is God saying
behold the man is now become as one of
us when he already said let us make man
in our what in our
likeness but I want you to watch
because that word become behold the man
has become as one of
us verse
22 let's read it again the Lord said
behold the man is what become that word
become that same Hebrew word become
watch this is translated in Genesis 3:1
behold the serpent was more subtle the
serpent was more subtle that's the word
that is translated was past tense was
check this
out what God is saying and that actually
saying in Genesis 3:22 is
Behold The Man Who was like
us look at the man that we created that
was like us look at the one that we
created in our image look at what he has
become as a result of his
sin one scholar actually translates it
this way here's what he says commenting
upon Genesis 3:22 he says and God said
behold the man has become as one of us
not spoken in irony as is generally
supposed but in deep compassion the word
should be rendered behold what has
become of the man who was as one of
us look at what happened to him as a
result of
sin because you see what Satan was doing
remember the Bible says in in in Isaiah
chapter 14 that Satan himself wanted to
be like God but his understanding of
what it meant to be like God was messed
up so when God creates a man he is
showing Lucifer this is what it means to
be like God it does not mean what you
think it means it means Perfection it
means Holiness it means righteousness so
man was a rebuke to
Satan this is what it means to be like
God so to be like God means means to be
Godlike in
character when man sought to become God
not just be like God but to become God
he lost dominion over everything
including the Animal
Kingdom Under Satan's rule listen
carefully guys under Satan's
rule man now resembles not the image of
God but the image of
beasts want you to think about what I
just
said under Satan's rule man is no longer
in the image of God man is now in the
image of the Beast y'all are not
catching
this you say how well listen Genesis 4
uh verse 1 speaking of Cain and Abel and
how Cain kills his brother let me ask
you a question is that
animalistic did Cain exhibit animalistic
Behavior yeah when we get to Genesis
chapter 6 and the Bible says the
thoughts of men's Hearts were only evil
continually was man beginning to
experience was man experiencing
animalistic tendencies
remember God had made man in the image
of himself but sin turned man into the
image of
beasts now please follow this hold your
place here in in Genesis and come with
me to the Book of Daniel chapter 4
because I need to illustrate this to you
Daniel chapter 4 Daniel chapter 4 and uh
if you are familiar with the content of
Daniel chapter 4 you will know that in
that chapter Nebuchadnezzar who everyone
Nebuchadnezzar has a dream and in this
dream he sees a great big
tree and the tree reaches onto heaven
and then he sees this Angel come and
cuts down the tree how many of you are
familiar with this Vision the angel cuts
down the tree and then a voice is heard
saying put a stump upon it and let seven
times pass over it and let a a
beasts let's read it
Genesis 4 I'm sorry Daniel
4 Daniel 4 verse
13 uh uh Daniel or Nebuchadnezzar
speaking here say says I saw in the
visions of my head upon my bed and
behold a watcher and a holy one came
down from heaven and he cried aloud and
said thus heue down the tree cut off his
branches shake off the leaves and
Scatter his fruit let the Beast get away
from under it and the fowls from his
Branch nevertheless leave the stump of
his roots in the earth even with a b
band of iron brass in the tender grass
of the field and let it be wet with the
Dew of Heavens let his portions be let
his portion be with the what with the
beasts in the grass let his heart be
changed from man's and let a
what let a what everyone BEAST's heart
be given unto him and let seven times
pass over him now let me ask a question
how many of you know what this tree was
was was symbolic of who did the tree
represent it represents presented
Nebuchadnezzar you remember what
happened to Nebuchadnezzar what happened
to
him he went mad he became like a what
for how long seven years why did he
become like a
beast his
what that tree reached onto
Heavens right Nebuchadnezzar is walking
in his P look at this Kingdom that I
have
built and when he does that
that time prophecy begins he becomes
like a wild beast now let me ask a
question why do you think Nebuchadnezzar
becomes like a beast because of
his because of his pride because of his
sins because of his pride because of his
sins he turns from a
man to a
beast hope you're getting uncomfortable
in your seats right
now because Nebuchadnezzar is not the
only
person to struggle with
pride you see
Beloved the
animal
kingdom when man lost his
Dominion he became subject
to things he was not subject to
before to behaviors and attitudes that
he was not subject to
before beasts are no longer under the
Dominion of man since the
fall we no longer have dominion over the
Beast we no longer have dominion over
the beasts from the
sea we no longer have dominion over the
beasts of the
Earth from the earth we no longer have
dominion over the Beast the flying
beasts in the sky as a result of sin we
lost dominion over this world if you're
with me so far just just let me hear you
say
Amen the Kingdom of man in essence has
become the kingdom of
beasts Cain killing Abel the wickedness
Before the Flood Sodom and Gomorrah
Joseph's brothers selling
him sound animalistic to
you think about what this planet has
become think about today think think
about our political environment
today think about our social environment
today we are living in a kingdom of
Peace might I even say even in the
church we are watching people who should
be behaving in the image of God
behaving we are living we are surrounded
by
Kingdom of
beasts and see you're thinking man I
don't want to be alive in the time when
the
Beast I don't want to be around in the
time when the when we have to face the
Beast beloved we are facing the Beast
now every nation that has ever lived has
had to face face the
beasts so then it is no wonder since sin
since sin came into this world man who
were supposed to reflect the image of
God began to reflect the image of the
Beast God is saying to man listen the
kingdom of men has become the kingdom of
Beast so it is no wonder that when we
get to the Book of Daniel chapter 7 we
find there a vision of
four beasts what do those beasts
represent the kingdoms of of
men are you catching
this God is using animals to show what
the world is
becoming so first we see this lion
rising up out of the out out of the Sea
and the lion represents the kingdom of
Babylon but we know that a lion is known
for its
ferocity that's a characteristic of
beasts fierce
then we see a beer a bear and the Bible
says of this bear in this same vision
the bear was to arise and devour much
flesh so here we see a devouring Beast
beloved a characteristic of the beastly
nature is when we is let me rephrase
that is when beasts devour beasts like
to
devour we see a leopard in this same
vision and the leopard is known for its
camouflage it looks one
way you can't even see it
coming but it sneaks up on you and
beloved that is a characteristic of
beasts and then we have that fourth
Beast who who who exceeding strong and
stamps with its feet and destroys
everything in its path that is the
characteristic of beasts
so come I need you to see this come back
with me to the Book of Revelation
Revelation 13 listen beloved these
attributes swiftness the leopard
devouring camouflage ferocity strong
exceedingly Pride Dreadful terrible all
are attributes listen carefully to me
all are attributes of the unconverted
human
hearts so when we're talking about man I
want to face the Beast guess what the
Beast is inside of
you y didn't catch
that every generation has had to face
the Beast because the Beast is inside of
you the Beast is inside of
me these
attributes exceeding Fierce camouflage
Swift devouring
beloved that's in our nature our
animal
nature so you need to see this come back
with me Revelation chapter 13 Revelation
chapter 13 because check this out guys
Revelation The Book of Revelation
describes four different beasts from
four different locations you need to see
this Revelation chapter 13 and verse one
Revelation 13:1 so the Bible says here
and I stood upon the sand of the what
sea and saw a what Beast rise up out of
the sea this Beast is described as
having seven heads 10 horns and in the
very next verse let's go to the very
next verse this Beast was like a leopard
his feet was a feet of a bear his mouth
is the mouth of a lion and the dragon
gave him his power seed and great
Authority this is the same Beast we just
read about in Daniel chapter 7 where is
this piece
from where is it
from this see is there another Beast
that comes up in Revelation 13 where's
he from the earth so watch this
guys when God made man and gave him
Dominion did God give man Dominion in
Genesis 1:26 over the beast from the sea
did he give him dominion over the beasts
from the Earth but when man lost
Dominion the beasts lost
control the end result beloved listen
carefully the end result of man losing
Dominion is right
here because now we have a beast coming
up out of the sea and what is that Beast
trying to do to the kingdom of
men what is he trying to do to the
kingdom of God destroy it this beast
from the earth that comes up out of the
earth what is he trying to
do destroy the kingdom of God the
Beloved the end time is about beasts
trying to gain dominion over
men this is the end result of us not
having the image of God when we lost the
image of God the image of the Beast took
over and it is a it is as a result of
men living in the image of the Beast
that by the time of the end we have
these beasts that are now turning on the
people of God and Waring against them
the dragon who is of the air the beast
from the sea which is from the sea the
beast from the earth which is from the
Earth and there's a beast from the abyss
all four beasts have turned on
man listen to me that beast from the
from the earth or from the sea that was
a persecuting Beast the beast from the
earth the horns of a lamb but speaks
like a dragon that Beast represented
hypocrisy how many of us struggle with
hypoc don't raise your
hand hypocrisy pretending to be one
thing but you're really
another that's the beast from the earth
the beast from the sea the beast from
the abyss you all know this because
you're Bible scholars the beast from the
abyss represents the French
Revolution which is atheism beloved
Satan is using any means possible he
will use atheism he will use hypocrisy
he will use persecution to try to bring
the Beast out of
you that's his goal because if he can
bring the Beast out of you then he
already has you in his kingdom even if
you don't go to church on the wrong day
of the week
all he needs to do is is to get you into
his kingdom and
you you are
worshiping the
image of the
Beast that means a question you and I
have to ask is wow who image am I in
today am I in the image of the Beast or
I or am I in the image of
Christ because God's trying to move man
to His Image but Satan is trying to move
man to the image of the
Beast
listen what does Christ want us to
understand it's very simple how many of
you aware that the Bible says that
Christ was the expressed image of his
father all right so the expressed image
of his of the father came to this Earth
so that we could Behold Him and by
beholding him be changed into the same
image now if he's changing me into the
image of God I must not have been in the
image of God before so if I'm not in the
image of God before and there's only one
other image what other image is that it
is the image of the
Beast God is trying to move me from
being the image of the Beast to the
image of
Christ now just to demonstrate to you
that Christ knew where he was coming but
listen to me the Bible says in Luke 2:7
that when Christ came to this earth he
was
born among
animals he was born among beasts he knew
he was coming to a kingdom that was
being run by animal in
instincts he was coming to a kingdom
that was that was that was run that was
dominated by those animal instincts
which is I am better than you I am
greater than you I deserve I deserve
this is what Jesus came to this earth to
destroy he came to destroy the kingdoms
of the
beasts and so beloved by beholding
Christ we become remade In His Image and
after his likeness and remember this
when we become in the image and likeness
of God God gives us again dominion
over the
beasts that's why he's come to give us
dominion over what we once had dominion
over now now don't please some of you
are jumping ahead and going oh yes so we
will be victorious over the beast at the
end of time no beloved you're thinking
ahead too far
because before we can overcome the beast
at the time of the end we must first
overcome the
Beast and what Satan is seeking to do is
just what he did with Eve listen you can
don't be like God become God say pastor
we know we can't become god listen you
don't have to you don't have to
literally become a supernatural being
that has has no beginning and no ending
to become God all you need to do the
Book of Ezekiel 28:1 and2 said of said
of this king of Tyrus because you have
said in your heart I will sit in the
seat of God I will be God what does it
mean to be God it simply means to sit in
his
seat God's seat is his
throne that's where that's the place
from where God makes
decisions a king makes decisions from
his
seat listen carefully guys when you say
I will make my own decisions about my
life you have made yourself
God you sit in the seat of authority I
decide for myself what I will do and
when you do that you have no control
over the Beast
Jesus says let me sit on the throne of
your heart and I will restore you in my
image and when I restore you in my image
you will have dominion
over the
Beast the beast from the sea that likes
to persecute others the beast from the
earth who likes to play the hypocrite
the beast from the abyss who likes to
say ah God doesn't see God doesn't even
exist yeah the beast from the from the
air the Dragon who who who seeks to
destroy and trample and all those
attributes will be overcome in you if
you let Christ dwell in you and listen
carefully to
me if you want to know how you will do
against the beast at the time of the
end just check out how you are doing
against the Beast right here
because the indication that you will
gain victory over the beast at the time
of the end is very simply how do you
gain victory over the Beast right
here come with me to Revelation 15 we're
getting ready to close Revelation
15 Revelation 15 and verse 2 and you
need to see this Revelation CH 15 and
verse 2 the Bible says here and they
sing the song of Moses the servant of
God
I'm sorry Revelation
15 right verse two verse two and I saw
as it were a sea of glass mingled with
fire and them that had gotten the
victory over the
who stop for a
second come
on come
on you know how you were reading that
verse before right all right man we're
going to go up against I am not going to
keep a false day of the
week if I can just claim that I will
gain the victory
no those that stand on the sea of glass
who gained victory over the Beast yes it
includes that Beast it includes that end
time power but the reason they got
victory over the end time power is
because they got victory over the Beast
right here
and beloved listen to me you and I fight
the Beast every day every generation
that has ever lived has had to face the
Beast and it has been a battle to the
death so if you're thinking I don't want
to be alive in this in this time because
it's a battle to the death you're
already in a battle to the
death you're already in the fight of
your
life I love this because in Revelation
chap 15 somewhere around there the Bible
says that there's coming a time where
the kingdoms of the earth will become
the kingdoms of the
Lord I don't know if you you catch the
beauty in
that the kingdoms of the earth what were
those what kind of Kingdoms
what kind of Kingdoms were they they
were animal
kingdoms the kingdoms of the
Earth have become the kingdoms of our
you remember Jesus said the kingdom of
God
is within
you there is a Time coming where people
who lived their
lives don't sound
crafts like
animals are going to catch a hold of the
of the beauty of the man Jesus
Christ and their characters are going to
be changed from the image of the Beast
to the image of
God and when Jesus comes again all those
kingdoms that belong to this world will
become the kingdoms of our
Lord and Jesus I'm going to invite
Andrew to come forward he's going to
pray for us Jesus says
at that time there will be no more
crying No More Pain No More Tears you
want to know why check this out guys
because the
beasts will be
cast into the Lake of
Fire and there will be no more Beast
Kingdom throughout all eternity
beloved if you want to be if you want to
celebrate that day you must get victory
over the Beast now